# **EOIN MCLAUGHLIN**

### PERSONAL DETAILS

Email Address: <a href="mailto:eoinmclaway@gmail.com">eoinmclaway@gmail.com</a>

Contact Number: 07456613387

National Insurance Number: Can be provided upon request

# PERSONAL STATEMENT

I have excellent organizational and communication skills which I have developed and use to provide excellent customer service in a busy bar environment. With the experience I have gained from working in a bar environment, I can perform and excel both working individually or as part of the team.

### **SKILLS**

- Communication With working in a bar environment communication is key in order for the customer to be satisfied, therefore I have to listen carefully to understand the order so I'm able to provide the best service possible.
- Teamwork I work effectively as a team player both within work and in my
  personal life as part of a Gaelic Football team. With these experiences combined I
  have gathered a better understanding on how to perform within a team not only
  to better myself but to influence the team to work more efficiently and
  effectively.
- Computer Skills While having a keen interest in computers, I learn quickly how to understand and operate different computer systems that different jobs require. This allows me to be more versatile in any job that I am required to do.
- Adaptable With working in a bar, I have been able to become adaptable to work
  at different paces. This has taught me to prioritize different tasks in order for the
  team to achieve the overall goal while also providing the best service possible to
  the customer.

# PREVIOUS EMPLOYMENT

# St Paul's GAC Sports Bar - Bar Staff

January 2015 – November 2017

# **Duties:**

- Bar tendering duties.
- Provide Customers with a range of Beverages including draught beer
- Ensure fridges are kept stocked with different beverages ensuring the team can perform efficiently.
- Handle cash transfer between the customer and myself including till and card machine transactions.
- To ensure the floor space and other areas of the bar are kept clean and tidy for customers.
- Ensuring all glasses are cleaned and displayed for use.
- Changing beer kegs when required.

# Féile An Phobail - Bar Staff

August 2017 & 2018

### **Duties:**

- Bar Tendering duties
- Ensuring beverages where available for the cashier so the service to the customer was efficient.
- Ensuring stock of glasses for use.
- Stocking the bar to ensure service is continuous.
- Ensure all floor areas are kept clean each day and presentable for the following night.

Amadeus – Casual Multi Skilled Operative (Formerly)

October 2017 - May 2018

Hospitality Belfast - Casual Multi Skilled Operative

May 2018 - Ongoing

# Waterfront Hall and Ulster Hall

#### **Duties:**

- Bar Tendering duties
- Ensuring beverages where available for the cashier so the service to the customer was efficient.
- Ensuring stock of glasses for use.
- Stocking the bar to ensure service is continuous.
- Ensure all floor areas are kept clean each day and presentable for the following night.
- Ensuring food presentation is maintained through service during dinners.
- Serve food to customers when working at retail points.
- Count till and float at the end of an event.

### **Duties:**

- Set up Executive lounges for high profile events
- Set up areas for hospitality use
- Ensure retail points are set up correctly according to stock allocation.
- Bar Tendering duties
- Ensuring beverages where available for the cashier so the service to the customer was efficient.
- Ensuring stock of glasses are cleaned and polished and readily available for use.
- Stocking the bar to ensure service is continuous.
- Ensure all floor areas are kept clean each day and presentable for the following night.
- Ensuring food presentation is maintained through service during dinners.
- Serve food to customers when working at retail points.

Carphone Warehouse - Customer Service Assistant

October 2018 - Ongoing

### **Duties:**

- Use POS and tablets to provide customers the product they would like
- Ensure the shop is clean and in an appropriate manner for customers to be satisfied
- Ensure all phones are cleaned before start of working day
- Ensuring all price tiles are correct on all products
- Ensuring all products are displayed properly and in an orderly manner
- Ensuring no messes are left on the shop floor
- Hoovering and washing floors before start of day
- Ensuring all doors are locked and alarm system is activated.

HSC Business Services Organisation - 1 Week Work Experience

January 2017

### **Duties:**

- Shadowed the web team and learned how to create a web survey using the tools that they use.
- Shadowed the desktop team and how they distribute and cater for the clients needs.
- Shadowed the services team and how they provide a service to clients through the different technology used.
- Shadowed the security team and how they implement policies to protect the internal network of the business.

# EIR NI -1 Week Work Experience

January 2016

### **Duties:**

- Set up the company laptops to ensure they're compliant with security protocol
- Learned how to search for a network intrusion and where it occurred.
- Learned how the IT Service desk team helps clients get their network back online.

# QUALIFICATIONS

7 GCSE'S (Grade A-C) August 2015

Including Maths and English

3 AS Levels (Grade B-D)

August 2016 & 2017

Including Digital Technology and Sports Science

3 A Levels (Grade CCD)

August 2018

• Including Moving Image Arts, Digital Technology and Sports Science

Duke of Edinburgh Bronze Award

June 2013

# **HOBBIES AND INTERESTS**

My major hobby is sport. I currently play Gaelic Football for school and club, while playing this I have developed many relationships with people from other clubs, counties and sports. However, from a young age I've had a huge interest in technology and computers. As I've got older this interest kept developing persuading me to follow a career in IT as well as my interest in technology. I have kept up to date on the new technology releases from headphones to mobile phones. I have a keen interest in photography and videography. This gives me a form of expression that I previously didn't have and it has allowed me to achieve many different things which I was unable to achieve before. It has also given me different opportunities that I previously wouldn't have achieved. Combining these, it has given me the ability to be driven to achieve many things together with a team and individually. I have a huge interest in technology especially computers where I learned a lot of what I know today. With this interest I have achieved some of my personal goals which include building my own computer and the network in my house.

# REFERENCES

Can be provided upon request